scanneranswers.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy | ScannerAnswers

**If you have any questions, please[contact us](https://scanneranswers.com/contact-us/)**

Want to request data that we’ve stored? **[Data Access Request](https://scanneranswers.com/data-access-request/)**

**Here’s our**[ **Terms of Use Page**](https://scanneranswers.com/terms-of-service/)

## Amazon Affiliate Disclosure

ScannerAnswers.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com

_*Amazon_ and _  the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc, or its affiliates_

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://scanneranswers.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### 

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

If you use our contact form, it will send us an email to our GMAIL account. We do not save or store your form submissions on our servers but we will keep them in our GMAIL account unless asked for them to be deleted. We do not use your email or the information submitted for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you are an admin and edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics for tracking how many visitors have reached our site. We do not use this information for marketing or anything other than seeing how many visitors we receive in a day. Here’s the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/)

## 

We are affiliates with Google Adsense as well as Amazon Associates. These are the only companies that we share data with. If we find that another company is involved, we will update this page.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Your contact information

We do not save your contact information on our servers.

## Additional information

— Old Policy for Historic Reference —

[ my_privacy_policy ] 

Summary

Article

Privacy Policy

Description

ScannerAnswers's Privacy policy page

Author

WebSite:

Scanner Answers
